Josh (Yahya) Al-Din

Objective and Goals

Develop a complete e-Commerce Portal and Platform for the Australian Medical B2B market, providing sourcing, logistical and analytical solutions to Australian businesses

Gain more experience in programming and data science to complement my MBA skills. Setup product road maps and strategies to launch and expand business operations, human resources and capital management.

I have a deep passion for implementing technology to complement, enhance and streamline business processes.

Education

2018 - Current (Part time)

Master of Business Administration (MBAx - Technology)

2018 - Current

- Full Stack Web Development Programming and Data Science Online
- Computer Science CS50 Harvard University
- MIT Micromasters in Data Science
- MIT Machine Learning with
- Datacamp data science
- Udemy Digital Marketing Suite
- Udemy Complete SEO
- Zambesi workshops
 – Digital Marketing with Mark Baatse CMO Showpo
- Zambesi workshops

 Growth Marketing Andrianes Pinantoan of Growth at Canva and AirTasker
- Zambesi workshops- Email Marketing that Works

2006- Current

 Membership of the Australian Association of Consultant Pharmacy (AACP)

2001- Nov 2005

Otago University, Dunedin, NZ

B.Pharm., Bachelor of Pharmacy.

Personality traits

Curious, highly motivated, Professional, Organised, Quick learner, Excellent. Customer skills, Effective communicator, Responsible, Well presented, and adaptable.

I can bring to your business an essential combination of Professionalism and customer service and technological skillset that is indispensable to modern business environment. As well as providing you with the edge, against competition.

Skills

Management, Business Strategy and Growth
Python 3 programming language, Numpy, Pandas, HTML, CSS. SQL
Selenium automation
Hubspot CRM and Automated Marketing
Google Adwords account manager.
Facebook ads account manager.
Mailchimp email marketing

Experience

2017 - Current

Pharmacist

Co-Owner, Consultant marketer and strategist for the Swan Clinic for Plastic Surgery

- Launch, Setup and implement marketing strategy for The Swan Clinic the marketing strategy and it implementation drove revenue to 150% year on year growth rate, annual revenue exceeds \$1million, from launching the business only 2.5 years ago.
- Liaise with key stakeholders, Surgeon and Staff to implement changes, and provide product owner ship, and organise for growth
- Leverage data analytics to improve market effectiveness.
- Shape public opinion and brand of Surgeon

2018 - Current

Digital Marketing for Boian Surgical Supplies Ltd

- Developed email, social media and general online presence for Boian.
- Expanded their product offering, and organised Youtube product demonstration to complement existing traditional marketing efforts.
- The first marketing campaign launched a new product for the company and sold over 200% predicted sales volume.

Founder of Pillpedia.com.au

- Developed a specialised medication review software for Pharmacies and Consultant Pharmacists in Australia.
- National sales of the software with an annual subscription model
- Consulting services to some customers, where I undertake the medication reviews on their behalf, with seamless cloud and database integration between clients to prevent duplication.

2008-Current

Consultant Pharmacist

- Undertaking Residential Medication Management Reviews for a total of 65 Nursing homes and Hostels around NSW
- In-service training for registered nurses to meet their accreditation requirements.
- Currently being trained to setup QUM's (Quality Use of Medicines Standards) for contracted Nursing homes as part of their funding and accreditation commitments

Consultant Pharmacist

- Sole Home Medication Review pharmacist for a number of pharmacies in the Sutherland Shire.
- Providing theses pharmacies with a professional image that can further establish their role as health providers and maintain their customer base in the face of increasing competition.

2006 - 2017

Pharmacist Manager (Kirrawee Pharmacy, Pharmacy 4 Less Caringbah)

- Managing and running a very successful pharmacy with large volume of foot traffic and, and very high script total per hour.
- Maintaining outstanding professional standards as well as customer loyalty and gratitude
- Maintaining high levels of standards and customer satisfaction as well as general management and organising staff to meet the pharmacy's large customer and professional needs.
- Oversight of the operational management and transformation of Business model to enhance competitiveness

References

On request